Thank you for this question, Julie.
Before we bring the work, I'm the United States of the team.
I'm doing this case, but I'm on firework.
We've got to thank you for this.
I thank you for your attention here.
I ask God that she knew this community was it.
I thank you for the council.
At the time, they spend like this better.
I thank you for the raise for our arms and what they're doing
and this community to help it.
I ask God that you want to be with all of this guy
and the citizens of the United.
We'll be with our families in Christ's name on prayer.
Amen.
One thing you would just do is like the United States of the United States.
And to give you an opportunity to thank the United States,
I'm on my nation, and I'm on firework.
And to this moment, the other team does this work.
Before we consent, I'm going to say that I'm going to say that I'm going to say that I'm going to say
the United States of the United States of the United States of the United States of the United States.
Then we want to say if you can do anything.
It was something that Events in the génilation prime.
I'm going to pull it out.
I'm talking about it.
I've got some of the people.
Any talk about the leaders of your citizens?
Well, second.
Six seconds.
Michael, couple.
Five.
Eight.
Six.
One second, five.
Five seconds.
Five.
Eight.
Second.
In the next week, we will be in the position of the e-cule.
I'll address that review of all the submissions and staff recommendations for seeing.
We'll go in on that 16th.
I'll go running because we are 21, 22.
Hello, yes, this is just for just like it on the concrete and everything else. This is for on cold boring.
We put it out for the place by some other food.
Some other things that are included in the packet and these were the three lowest vendors.
I mean, I don't know where I'm going, it's an uprising of the building.
Instruction. So we're asking for approval time.
So we use all three of these.
Or one of the three things.
Well, let's call it for the opposite of the lowest one person.
And then they said, hey, you know, what do you want to have something that maybe gives you the second one or third one?
Let's, when I'm going to do those, first one.
Yes, so that's the next one.
Why would they say different?
They have a dude, yes, actually.
Which one of them closest to us?
Or call it, do you want them?
Who's the closest in location united?
They're out of the day.
So that's their first call, and they're also the cheapest.
They're cheap.
But I love it.
I honestly wonder if the other bunch didn't throw in the chair and they're called us for the price difference.
I don't know.
The group award name contract, I review.
I've all did solutions to that recommendations.
You can go to the next one.
That's, I mean, on call.
Tricks do you deliver from this week?
Only once a week.
So I'm going to say the boring list of the just open trends.
So you do it.
You put those BEC or GD, water line, and then cover it back at it.
The city is a lot of materials.
Your contract will just be the latest portion.
For those of the same contractors.
Yes, first thing united is the same party.
I'm calling it, and treptured, and then it would be different.
They don't forward.
So do we not do the adventure doing it for ourselves?
You know, we do.
But sometimes we just load our gang and police.
I don't know.
I have seven people.
So this is all of us.
Do some capital projects.
We don't have people.
So the G with it.
I do.
Well, as all my partners say, I'd like to do capital projects and have.
But we just don't have people.
Did you add people?
Did you?
I would say yes.
I'll let Chris explain on that.
I would say a big teamer, other than the United Express.
I'm going to be looking at their prices.
They're pretty cheap.
Yeah.
to be asked what to do and for less than one day. I guess with our budgets, our main
sector is to share the bottom of the problem that we do for your talent. But the budget
is not the fine-honest of the world, but it's just a period of time. But I'm going to be telling you
to be the far part of the consideration of the technical and the critical pattern of the session
of the session. But that's something that's kind of a demo that we're not going to take
that the consideration for the future of the institution that we're going to be offering
is sufficient for us. But you can either take it in the chat. It's a very wrong thing
that we're going to be sure that we're going to sit in something that's fine. Through years,
you've got enough of something.
And if you get after it, it'll be a great picture. They've also been working with you in this group.
So that's one thing that we're going to work with. We have to have a morning and I'm going to say we have all that
people going to do your teaching. So we have all those people going to do what I'm going to do,
which is how people are turning around.
Chris can type some funny stories when you want to mainstream about all the people that yell that out.
You have a question, though.
You want to do a group?
Well, you've set over to get satellite, but you can do a wardrobe and see.
Probably one of those here is something we're simply in the living room of one.
We've got to go down to work, run, puller, puller, puller, puller, puller, puller, puller.
Okay, there. And now we're going to go down to 47,000.
I brought Terry for the talk about the TV thing after that.
This is what I can say, it's sort of important to work with wood.
So the guys are requesting our tools to go out and wire our system.
We got ready for these important ideas to do not have one.
And we're going to clean it up.
So we'd like to be able to share your talk about the need for having to use if you have any more questions on that.
Often we use those.
Often when you're ready.
When you're ready to go, we'll do that.
And when you're ready to go, we'll do that.
Yeah.
I need to get ready to use those four to five times.
We used, but I saw a man on a trailer that didn't reach the whole line of the way that the woman
realized it was just a trailer, just a whole lot of wire, because that would have been high
I don't know what's on it anymore, what do they live in?
We served once in and then we realized that we had, when we did it, we had a piece of heating unit,
and everybody wanted it.
I think we had, we had three months to actually take a living room.
What do you do now for people, some of you just ran on?
Well, I like to try to get rid of it, I don't know what we thought.
We ended up, because that's kind of more country.
Out there, we had a couple of taxiway across, we ended up taking a couple of outages on to the line and just going over it.
And in a single phase, the money one plays at, and then pulled me out of the green on the ground, and then went all the way up,
and then it ended up supposed to be for people.
That's not what the reason we wanted to do that, and then I'm not quite a fool of them,
because all of them came across, both drugs, service drugs, things like tax.
You really didn't really end that with this type of machine,
but only if you're not going to take a cab, it's full of that.
So probably, I'm kind of trying to promise you we had to end up with, this will be easy.
So we had a Peter 23, which, you know, when you personally came to the council to acquire the equipment for the alleys,
we're also going to do there on 19th, 19th, 19th, and we bring the order to the L.A.
Those, those, those, those old, and a lot of contractor do that,
but we will take it from other contractor's stops on that sort of substation,
and then back out into the Southwoods, some other property.
So here, 169, I have a big six-time, I know, or why in 169, I have a putting out infrastructure out there.
So if you don't take this, are you going to run home?
Yes, I'm going to run there.
How long have you had, I don't think I'm going to take these projects over a year or two.
I mean, they're probably getting, it's getting that, because everybody's out doing infrastructure.
So once you get it, you're going to have for a year, I'd say at least.
I mean, I was like, that's really a fantastic type of question because, you know,
some of the lines were going to remind you that there's been almost kind of there.
You know, we even don't go around on the project, but it's super busy.
And we're going to be very proud to be able to go on the course.
They don't particularly need a machine.
They'll be going to be there for, probably, on and off for a month.
So, they're going to have to use it with that.
and this is why I'm doing a no-get in a school and so it's,
I'm going to make it.
So it's just a bit of what we got going on,
a lot of times we were on a project,
we're on a next slide.
So we got a lot of this over the Northwest,
we got a lot of the polls, a lot of the polls,
a lot of the danger, any requests,
any, just any requests, any, at the end of this time of the season.
So if we had it for a year,
maybe we'd use it for three months of the pandemic,
but probably we'd use it for going on,
but I don't have to admit that the nature of how much of that,
we wouldn't be used for over three years.
But what's your energy and deep from your perspective?
I guess that would be,
or maybe over ten months,
that would help us to have a lot of those at this,
a few projects, you've got to hold the term.
These are sort of five times a month.
Yes, sorry, we never got to take that out of that sort of thing,
but I don't know.
How long will these carry the last year?
I don't know if they're on the line.
This is one thing to see the difference in the two machines there.
And you see the more expensive moment,
it's not the way if,
we didn't take the moment,
but it's not the same type of machine.
The one that we spoke at was a turret product,
or like these high hours and stuff you can get in there,
and the whole machine rotates at half of it,
and it's trying to align with these big old brainers
that keep holding line like you do.
So it's got a turret amount.
It might affect when we put it in the oven,
but we couldn't get that out of the oven.
So it's the growth further.
Trainers, you know,
I want to have this specific machine,
or if there are other problems,
how does it fit in the top?
There are fewer,
more than that.
I believe that the surely right,
the machine is actually built up,
and I thought it was just a regular one.
And when they can get it out,
well,
we've created these big,
and I'll say fun together.
They're not a big,
but we have to act a lot.
We've got proof for it,
and this is the year until we,
we're like,
we went into that,
we went into this,
that's what we are.
So that's already been approved
to budget,
and you have to money,
or all right,
at the same time.
They don't have any of these out there use awesome time to anything like that that you've seen
We've put it out forward. They wanted to, you know,
I was the one, we did a bit of a lot of that stuff.
The difference between the two, the capsule and the four and four and one point,
just people don't have any contact right.
That's correct. The one board said,
it's got a door to the old, four rows of doors, and you just turn the old thing,
because then positioning the door to the line,
which makes it.
With our average, I would say,
that I would say that I'm a pack of things.
I don't want to use this anymore.
I have to double check what I think it will lead you.
If something goes wrong with it,
then it doesn't have to work on it.
Does that have a lot of our expensive stuff?
The first year in working,
you know, that ain't not necessary.
Often, or you're going to use an after,
everything's done.
I was saying that you wanted to do something.
But only that,
that being paid down, I think it's all.
But we're going to use it for continually.
If you guys know this,
if not for this, you probably could have done it.
All this online,
because it's still in place.
I think there's lots of them.
And you don't have to add,
you don't have to add, you don't have to add a quarter of a week.
I can say it for a quarter of a week too,
but it's just that they're just seeing,
hopefully, all of that.
That's what we respect on how high that was.
So we do all of those.
And we are going to do one seven half.
I mean, next year,
we're going to propose a budget.
I have a pretty good apple that's been served.
But it's connected to your environment and you do.
And you said it,
and you don't have to worry about it.
I mean, you know, why I'm asking you to say something there?
If you want a river crossing the way you're back to New York,
that's why you can pass your life back to the 21st century,
and hopefully, certainly, working on it.
Yeah, I think I have to have that in the 21st century.
How many times can you get a river line to,
but only when it comes to time?
Other than that, it's located, like I said,
you know, there's a line that runs from elsewhere
where by the river tracks, all over the nursing home, all of Easter,
we did that line.
Besides that, at one time, it forces me to like sit in it.
It was held three days, one on that line.
It's a way that single place, all over the land, all at one side,
at this land, all around.
And, again, there's all the services, all around.
I mean, we just kind of work with all the hand,
and make work with all the hand.
And this piece of work will make your job safer.
I have to look at that.
That's why we can't simply say,
it's actually due to robbery.
So it's not going to be done if it's the only robes in,
and then you're pulling back over attention,
and that's going to be acknowledged.
If you can't hold any money, we're going to do that.
Yeah, it's all going to be 20, 20 grand on there.
And the only other page that I might call it getting into the 80, 80,
and that is 70.
I'm thinking of a society of time, but lots of time.
Yes.
Those are not any piece of equipment that's going to make it a problem.
Safe or an easier and safe time.
Make motion to the group.
Second.
Be set.
Five.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Five.
Seven.
Ten.
Three.
One.
Four.
So this is a total trigger, and it says that you won't hold it, and it's also got both
for it for putting it in a wire arm and then break something, and then pour it with that
tissue that you have to put it in, because you have to attach it on it, you have to put
it on your teeth.
And on the solar Moon, they just get, they get prerise on it so that it does it pretty
cool and comes up on the soil.
So, you know, I have those holes for the inside of the trailer, the process has taken
a little, pulling all the living, all the things in the water, all the things in the water,
all the water in the pan.
It could follow the current survey.
If you can't do this, you can't say that it is further than 125, that we know just
haven't delivered it enough.
The witches are the option anyway.
But we asked the cities and some doctors to follow me.
So we could move on next.
We could put them on the ground.
So this was trying to take care of that goal of the streets.
We don't have to be currently doing that at all.
We do have a vehicle where it is.
It's just over your neck out there.
But there's no tire going into the time itself.
You have to put it to the table.
You can give it aнов to the rest.
And a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit.
A little bit of air.
I mean, you can throw the highest of the air.
It's a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of a little bit of air.
You can throw the highest of the air.
It's definitely the most difficult in the street hall.
And as we keep going out the small trill rate up here for you here to give it to you.
And as some of those are literally pulled out of the trees up there.
I mean when you're home three tri...
It's three poles at a time you can't really get a lot of poles there.
You can't really get a lot of gold down until very fast, so you know if you want to trade it, you just keep going on the credit, just go listen to them off with a deer, but where they ain't in that stuff.
And you can do a different credit home.
How to do it?
In the side of the pole.
I'm going to say, you're all well.
What do you want to do?
I'm going to put it to the point where you're going to do what you want to do.
I'm assuming it's the same thing.
I'm going to say that.
I'm going to say that again.
I'm going to take you.
The thing often doesn't use.
Because without just reading on this.
We've been out for a bit.
It's not something like the use option.
I'm going to say that.
We're going to buy a credit for using.
What we have on this is the board.
And it is difficult to buy as a piece of equipment used.
Because you have to ask them to hold a piece of equipment.
And we can thank you.
We have to prove that we have to buy as a piece of equipment.
And then our process is difficult sometimes.
When you just pull up on my options.
I'm going to say we have about one piece of equipment.
like I said, but we've been now, we usually give the object to give us the balance
of use because sometimes we give that a lot of times they don't.
And we're going to go through the process of that in our furniture and we refer to it.
It's not necessarily the same type of thing.
I mean, it's a whole thing.
But it's unbelievable how it's said, it has to go through a lot of times.
But it's not like I think we need those options if you like.
And it's also been like this.
I've got somebody who's not already working.
Because you may not want to have the terms that you've used,
but I suppose those ones are probably correct.
Yes, sir.
Second.
Please stand.
14.
Exactly.
That's right.
We were getting all been to see where she came from, that's her mind.
We're simply in the delivery of one of our people.
And we were saying they're very, very much in the delivery.
Yes, sir.
That's the same.
A state statute is required to let the two people to take a front of the board.
I'm sure you check with this.
So we just, we'd like to read this out.
We always see one bit.
We had another bit of a bit.
But their patterns go.
They overnight.
But they're playing on the delay.
So we didn't have to be not open.
We'd decide someone option to let their pricing instead.
All right, guys.
I'll call my phone.
I'll put that on.
Thank you.
15.
The brew is in line.
We're going to buy a relation to work sheet.
And offer it in the mouth again.
That's a lot of respect.
Very genuinely.
But we're both a little trust.
We don't even know what to say.
So this is before each of these, when I'm 69, if you know, if we're going to have to
make two lines, 69, we are also putting in the same text to the right one, 69,
and most of their infrastructure, we do get that area more ready to develop.
And as part of that, we actively go through the back of the property.
And so this is one of these meant to be cross over the back of the property.
We're exactly that property.
Can you both be aware of this?
We're also 69, yeah.
So there's the house right there.
There is the Cuomo casino sign.
And there's the actual house.
And we're looking south, right?
Yes.
Yeah.
And people will line their house.
Yes, sir.
So, you know, we run the risk.
If you put it in the front here, then you'd be in O.D.
Seasman and within wife.
And that eventually we have to remove.
We have to relocate it at the city's cost.
So by us buying the easement in the back of the property.
And we would have to relocate anything.
Because that being done in the city.
Some of that is some of that we, there's a change in our parcel that we have.
I think it was kind of a kind of a rather middle-aged platform for the city control.
Yes.
And we actually answered a little bit more.
I don't know if you can hear it from that.
For the earlier years, I believe that.
I know that.
But when I'm talking about sort of a house.
There's like five years on the eight years.
That's very valuable up to there.
And if that has to happen.
And if that's part of your day.
I don't know if this is something to see that.
So that's probably more of a price to pay to that kind of people.
At that year's, I'm based on the United States Services,
the University of Minnesota Services that I'm in from up to work.
They're not there for a dog.
And that's kind of the standard rate.
But it is a big set of trade-offs.
So they're paying a little bit more to relocate the text inventory.
They're pets or this is like a little lesson for people wearing their pets, which is their favorite idea of pets.
We'll note that for interviews.
And it is listed on the conversation sheet as far as you can really get to my parents' side.
Now that's a lovely offer.
So we're talking about approval from the MTA to offer that.
I'm sorry.
I mean, if I can get more to the rule 2 say about 2,000 dollars on the amount of time it needs.
I think they've done it.
They've done it.
So, we can start over.
I'm trying to dig on the property and put the infrastructure in and bury it in this so I can talk to you right?
Yes, so you also have a power line on it too.
So this is an error.
It's the end.
We'll be able to write mine in the office over there and possibly water.
If we were to move forward with offerings or a pruning out to pick up the laws of that change, what we were doing here,
I think you can do it with the context of the change.
So what an offer be made at five and see where we go or that's fine.
I mean, I think that might be a good thing.
That's what we like together when we have a lot of others involved.
So they make the offer, we make our rights or anything like offered.
Yeah, I'm sorry, sorry, did you get the question?
But I was just trying to clarify,
but I think UFS won't say that you got that.
Yes, I got that.
I'm like much more improved up to,
but you know, the initial offer is five.
That's five.
Eight.
Jump.
Six.
A.?
Nine.
I'm like two.
Six.
Four.
Five.
The first.
If they are strapped, it is not a latch.
Just six times.
Let's see what I'm seeing.
Yes.
I'm not afraid to say yes.
If you want to, I say that those, then do I think further,
but I think we can go back and go again on those particular items,
and you can figure out if you can send it up like this.
I'm going to send it up like this.
I'm going to do this.
So I'm going to do the consent to the last, the eye.
It's pretending to be the zero-eat of the hostage.
Here, you know that.
Maybe probably up to the back.
And we're sending it to this.
And there you go.
I'm going to send it to the other side.
I'm going to do this.
All right.
I'm going to do that.
Not that.
We've got the next week, so we're going to do this.
And then I'm going to now I'm going to make motion to prove
everything that we can send it to the acceptable,
and then we'll set the numbers to the acceptable.
So I'm going to do this.
I'm going to do this.
But I'll make motion to prove.
I'll second.
I'll just send it to the building.
It's in it.
Yeah.
It's out of the building.
Oh, make a motion to be a crew.
Exit in the mic.
The administrative, they drive a name and then go stack.
But to include the security meeting, how will purchase good Indian trajectories?
Yes.
You can include it on just a little bit.
Good thing.
Yeah.
Is that a good clue?
Exactly.
Is that a clue?
A clue?
All right.
These next time, put it right.
Thank you.
All right.
There's a little bit of a slide that we pulled out of the basement.
Yes.
But the reason I want to pull that out is because that's why I'm not here.
It's last year.
I didn't really see any items like this.
So openly, just throw them out there.
Here we go.
Here's something to mention.
We're dealing with with some of the litigation.
So I've been working towards the city.
And I thought it was really cool.
I think it's cool.
I think we're going to list it out there.
I think it's pretty cool.
Yes.
But it is transparent.
Because our citizens know what's going on.
That's the reason I want them to set aside.
Because it's clearly an attempt to be made to let folks know.
But we got going on.
And I think that's really cool.
So I'm trying to find out.
So to give the council a debate that they could leave the background.
Those particular items.
They should actually remain specifically.
Is our deal with critics as they're working on.
And also, in this case, it's really a deal.
And that in fact, the item in there, the world, the health track.
That gives the attorney that we have working on the work.
That has some other work for us as well.
These two items are not related to this.
It's safe to walk the subligation that we have.
I'm going to go to the United States and that subligation is specifically related to the work of people.
And that, a few, takes place in DC.
In the attorney's at the sea and at higher.
I'm going to show you how far back when it's been.
It's been seven years now.
They've been working on the happiness deal.
And it has came to a certain point.
that which we were needing to utilize in the brief
in the 60-month April, that's truly worth to this process.
And that has been provided to you all today.
That's something that was justified to us,
and we still know that I guess it is well.
And if you think about it, it is in there.
You also see where, during the day,
we'll have to respond to this brief.
They come a bit, which is next Thursday,
and there is on to this brief.
You will try to set the stage from where we go from here,
and try to produce decisions.
Those decisions that were made up of all the need,
could ask that they can act and utilize it itself.
And I think the icing thing is one.
In fact, it's a way that they operate the game.
We should all of them make the impact,
but it's a way that the life of that icing
is which we're being aware of,
we're going to apply to the situation,
we're going to prefer the easy, legal augmentation
as we're going to give it.
And it is a very interesting belief.
I think that's something that we need to put out publicly,
and then I will ask you a room today to publish that document,
and then you'll read the room website,
because I think it's something that I'll look at,
I'll look at something that will send,
and I think it's not important.
And it basically defines the history of the city environment,
and the planning issues that we have.
And it explains the only thing I've got here
or have, the challenge we have doesn't make it,
and we're going to be able to show that this is a very important document,
so it's a very, very, very, very, very interesting.
I'm going to be able to move on to the adoption
and then I'm going to be able to please select all the decisions.
I think it can work for citizens to know where these folks are going to go.
And this is a show where it's only going to go to the deep,
I don't personally like to highlight this impression
that they're going to be able to make it a public,
if they have the bottom of the website or the easy fact.
It is all a public information, but we have to make it a
level in a very, very, very long stick, not losing the process
like I kind of think of the background.
I think this may be easy.
It's easy that at home we're able to look at it and see,
because the one thing that people are thinking
is very, very expected, they're screened, they're policy,
it's going to work in it.
And it's going to be a simple policy, and they're still
going to realize the quality of the building,
the level of the public relations.
And another is a thought out there that we spent $3,000 in life
things to do.
and the knowledge and the skills that that's not to get so the majority of our money or the city's money,
the community money, as it has been on the deal of advice and you probably get to remember one of that.
And I'm not going to accept that today for that.
We're probably around 2.8 million people who have some big, big, big, year-to-year success.
That's how it is.
It's been 12,000 years.
This has been a real good condition.
In fact, the city is committed.
This impacts the way that the nation is offered.
That's the issue.
Why are you offering the info?
All of that is impacted.
Probably on that.
The way you respond to the majority of the action.
You respond to a certain distance.
You can bring all these levels of stream.
All of that is taken within the operation of it.
And that's what this is primarily about.
In the way the studies that we've had in the youth, we've had it in the past.
I know what study's done.
That basically could probably be impacted.
The presence of data is actually in the macro effect.
Being that has been proven in some of the second multiple times.
And I actually had an old work saved.
If you're correct.
You've been impacted by this work.
How are you?
The urban community.
Another issue that decided that the information of the young youth.
You decided not to follow.
Do not do anything about it.
You have to see a few.
That the climate says no.
There has to be a total of the area.
The area.
There.
Good thing.
Not that.
The area.
This area.
Most important part of it is just because of this.
And then how that flow is impacted since the day I did it was in the mountains of the shade of it.
This is a huge, really complex.
Some of those front-lights say that I have been away since I've been in this position for last night.
But I'm not, I've spent multiple hours in the power to the arch of the areas.
I'm understanding the complexity of this earth, you know, great.
And I can begin to talk about the fact that we gave it a stone to all of you today.
But if it's like a flexible person, not something that we do in a single category,
I think this is something we can talk about, how do we want to do to that special opportunity,
which is something that we've never seen.
The channels that we have in those lawsuits are important, how do we want to drive decisions to succeed?
But we have to make it all for it.
Because there are, in fact, things that we have to do,
I think it's something that's common to do,
I think, in by and similar to what all we've got to do,
to do this is to be presentations on the history of this.
Because we've done some of that, we've done some of that.
We've done some of that.
We've had one of our theories coming to get that presentation.
I think we've been out there and see what kind of education is further.
Even if we don't actually like to learn what they're saying is,
but it is something that is not something that you can just teach.
You know how to teach.
But putting this document in there, we can go along with you.
So I say, I'll let you kind of act in the original way,
but the exception is to talk about the transaction,
because these are expensive, expensive journey journey.
To hire a choice, take all of the filing with fur,
and wash it in, and find your people.
If they will listen to it, if there's not a cheap ticket,
you can just spend a different fall of the transactions there.
It's a priority for you right now.
We'll say, we're going to send you a thousand.
We're looking to do this issue.
Yes, I think it is.
There's something we've got to take out.
Third, second, one thousand.
Four hundred is doing something.
So we are not talking about small things.
And these things, they're the meaning,
how we're going to use these sessions and how we've been forward.
And I'm going to say that I want to advise it.
So I just want anybody to know that these decisions are not going to matter.
So the people in a state of violence, this one will be licensed in a new field.
So it will soon start to say that we will spend 300,000.
We have to do this with that.
We can recruit.
You know what I'm saying?
I have about 2,000 and 2,000.
And that 300,000 is always spent on that.
That also could be out of 3,000.
And all of a sudden, but the money we promised, the 300,000,
was just 60,000 to the next six,
because they couldn't afford it on the ground.
So the city front of that.
We're trying for those six and seven.
We get a portion of that back.
Okay?
Yes.
But it is 200,000.
It's a change.
It's a thought.
Of which we got 100,000 back.
So they're still.
some that we have committed to that role as this, that that also has a perceived role for technical assistance offered in these things.
Thank you.
Thanks for the clarification.
Thank you very much.
We've moved to the training and I have to consent.
One last thought.
The just clarification in the amount of the took where you started to think we're hard-rooted,
even if you're sure you'd like to.
The University of Kansas.
Yes.
The University of Kansas is the name of the University of Kansas.
Both of those attended.
Both of these initiatives are just relevant.
Both of the publishing and the stocking.
We're going to try to work with us.
If you don't want to know,
I'll be back with you.
Did the people run?
We would.
Some teams have to go.
You can hear the announcements.
They need to turn this.
So we'll.
Thank you.